Harry: It looks wrong.
Philip: Hmmm. It is wrong.
Richard: Are they always that difficult to make?
Philip: The truth is…yes. I’ll try again.
Robbie: At this rate, the wedding will take place tomorrow.
Philip: Not to worry. OK. Here we go.
Harry: I’m worried, Philip. What if we can’t tie the tie?
Richard: If we can’t tie the tie, then there can’t be a wedding.
Robbie: You’d better not make Harry any more nervous than he is. Don’t worry. We'll figure a way.
Grandpa: How’re you doing, fellas?
Harry: Not so good, Grandpa. We can’t get this bow tie tied. Nobody knows how to do it. Do you?
Grandpa: No. I never could, either.
Philip: Well, you have your own tuxedo. How do you tie your bow tie?
Robbie: Yeah, Grandpa, I’ve seen you in it. You look great. How do you tie it?
Grandpa: I don’t.
Richard: You don’t?
Harry: What do you mean?
Grandpa: I never could tie one of those…things…bow ties. I have always worn a clip-on bow tie.
Harry: A clip-on?
Philip: Of course. Now I remember.
Grandpa: Yes, it’s so easy. All you do is clip it around under your collar.
Richard: We all need one of those.
Robbie: The tuxedo rental store. Do you think they’re open?
Philip: Should be. Sunday’s their big day.
Richard: I’ll call and find out.
Grandpa: Well, if they’re not, I’ll lend you mine, Harry. You’re the only one who really needs to be wearing a tuxedo, anyway.
Harry: Thanks, Grandpa.
Philip: I’m the father of the bride. I’m supposed to be worried about my daughter, and here I am with the man that’s marrying my daughter-worrying about him.
Grandpa: Poor Harry. I know the feeling. Wedding-day litters.
Robbie: Are they open?
Richard: We’re in luck. They’re open. And they have lots of clip-on bow ties.
Robbie: I’ll bicycle down to the village and get them.
Harry: You’d better hurry, Robbie.
Grandpa: There’s lots of time. A little over two hours.
Harry: In two hours and fifteen minutes I’ll be married to Susan.
Philip: And be a true member of the Stewart family.
Grandpa: Oh, you’re a lucky guy, Harry. Susan is one of the best women you’ll ever find. She’s just like her grandma.
Richard: Now, once you put the ring on Susan’s finger, you are one of us, Harry. And don’t ever forget it.
Harry: Ring? Ring? Oh my! What did I do with the rings? I put them in the pocket of my sports jacket.
Richard: No, I think you put them in your tuxedo jacket pocket. Remember?
Harry: Right. What did I do with the rings?
Philip: Didn’t you give them to Richard? He’s your best man. I remember. You gave them to Richard.
Richard: Oh, yeah. I remember now. You handed them to me. What did I do with them?
Harry: I hope they aren’t lost.
Grandpa: Oh, don’t worry, Harry. They have to be here.
Richard: I remember. I gave them to Robbie to hold so I wouldn’t lose them.
Harry: Oh, I forget. What time is it?
Grandpa: It’s still a little over two hours, Harry. Just relax.
Harry: What about the rings?
Richard: I’m sure Robbie has them.
Harry: No, NO, Robbie doesn’t have them. He gave them to me to hold on to them because he didn’t want the responsibility of holding them. I put them in my tuxedo but in the lapel pocket. That’s a relent. I was really worried.
Richard: I’ll hold on to them for you. The best man always keeps the rings.
Harry: You’re right. You’re right. You hold on to them so there won’t be problem later.
Philip: Well, now, I think we’d better get dressed, fellas.
Grandpa: All right!
Richard: Robbie will bring the ties back.
Harry: Hey, leaving me?
Grandpa: You’ll be fine.
Philip: Try to take it easy. It’ll all be over in two hours.
Harry: Over?
Grandpa: The wedding ceremony will be over. You’ll be husband and wife.
Harry: I guess you’re right. Two hours from now. Two hours from now.